开什么玩笑呀
Are you kidding me?
乔伊
Joey?
乔伊  乔伊  乔伊
Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey.
乔伊 乔伊
Joey, Joey.
乔伊  乔伊  乔伊
Joey, Joey, Joey.
我吵醒你了吗
Did I wake you?
甘瑟  再给我来杯咖啡
Gunther, could I get another cup of coffee, please?
你下班后都做什么
So what do you do when you're not working here?
-你不必没话找话  -谢了
- You don't need to fill these silences. - Okay, thanks.
钱德勒  这都是你第4杯咖啡了
Chandler, that's your fourth cup of coffee.
我拼命喝咖啡  是因为困得要死
Well, I am drinking lots of cups of coffee because I'm exhausted!
因为乔伊开始打鼾了
Because Joey started snoring!
他睡在隔壁  有那么大声吗
He's in a different room. He's that loud?
你应该来听听
You should hear me.
这又不是什么光彩的事情
It's not something to be proud of, okay?
你得去睡眠诊所瞧瞧了
You have to go to a sleep clinic!
我说过  我才不要去什么诊所
I told you, I'm not going to any clinic.
我没有毛病  有毛病的是你
I don't have a problem. You're the one with the problem.
你该去"少任性别管我"诊所治治病
You should go to a "Quit-being-a-baby-and-leave-me-alone" clinic.
-根本就没有那种诊所  -当然有
- They don't have those. - Yeah, they do.
少任性  别管我
Quit being a baby and leave me alone!
这就是你的第一课
There, you just had your first class.
我跟一个睡眠很浅的人交往过
I used to go out with this guy that was a really light sleeper,
每次我打鼾  他就把我翻过去
and whenever I started to snore, he would just roll me over.
爽哦
Oh, yeah!
他帮我翻身  我就不会打鼾了
He would just roll me over and I would stop snoring.
下次你再打鼾  我就把你翻过去
Next time you snore, I'm rolling you over!
我打我的  你翻你的
I gotta do what I gotta do. You gotta do what you gotta do.
随你便
You just do it.
大家好
Hey, guys.
奥运主题曲
Oh, the Olympics!
-大喜之日定了吗   -还没
- Have you guys picked a date yet? - No. Not yet.
我还是不敢相信你订婚了
I still cannot believe you're engaged.
是因为你们进展太快
Just 'cause its happening so fast;
不是说你没人要
not 'cause you're such a loser.
谢谢  有人看到瑞秋了吗
Thanks. Has anyone seen Rach?
她在楼上"不"洗碗
She's upstairs not doing the dishes.
我告诉你  这次我绝不帮她洗
I tell you something! I'm not doing them this time!
就算碗盘堆在水池里
I don't care if those dishes sit in the sink
上面长满了...
until they're all covered with...
我回家就洗
I'll do them when I get home.
艾蜜莉在伦敦看中一件婚纱
Listen. Emily found this wedding dress in London...
-这么快  -对  但尺寸不合适
- Already? - Yeah, but it didn't fit.
幸好这里有家店还有一件她的尺码
Luckily, there's a store here with one left in her size.
但我是新郎  不能提前看到婚纱
But I'm the groom, I'm not supposed to see the dress...
-我去帮你拿  -谢谢
- I'll pick it up for you. - Thank you.
她让你跑腿  帮她拿婚纱
She's got you running errands, picking up wedding dresses...
哗啪
Wah-pah!
哗啪是什么
What's wah-pah?
就是鞭打啊
You know. Whipped.
哗啪
Wah-pah!
那才不是鞭打
That's not whipped.
鞭打是...
Whipped is...
这和我的有什么区别
That's what I did.
哗啪
Wah-pah!
你什么都不会
You can't do anything!
莫妮卡  我正在洗碗
Hey, Mon. I was just doing these dishes.
你有空吗
Do you have a minute?
有  反正我正打算休息
Yeah, yeah. I was just about to take a break anyway.
是这样的...
So listen...
我们还没有机会谈过
I know you and I haven't really had a chance to talk...
自从艾蜜莉和我决定结婚后
since Emily and I decided to get married.
我想知道你好不好
And I was just wondering how you were.
如果是你要结婚  我会觉得有点...
If you were getting married, I would feel kind of...
-你懂吗  -懂  懂
- You know? - Yeah, yeah.
我的确吓了一跳  不过...
It definitely took me by surprise. But, you know...
我很好
l'm okay.
我只是想确认一下
I just wanted to check.
你真好  谢谢
That's sweet. Thank you.
你真好
You're great.
有一天你也会找到自己的真命天子
And I know someday this will happen for you too.
撑着点
You just hang in there.
"Hang in there"?
不  我的意思不是...
No, I didn't mean...
难道你没听说我和约书亚
Maybe you haven't heard of a serious relationship
正爱得死去活来吗
called "me and Joshua"?
你们不是才约会4次吗
I thought you had just been on like four dates.
我不知道你们开始认真了
I didn't realize that had become anything.
我们是认真了
Oh yeah. Oh no no, it has become.
那4次约会棒到不行
Oh no, those were four great dates.
我们很般配
I mean, and the connection!
情感上  心灵上...
I mean, you know, emotionally, mentally. You know?
肉体上
Physically.
-太好了  -可不是嘛
- That's incredible. - I know, isn't it?
我跟约书亚在一起  你跟艾蜜莉在一起
I'm right there with Joshua. You are right there with Emily.
就像是...我们打成平手了
And it's kind of like it's a tie.
我得继续洗碗了
I gotta get back to my dishes.
我得去上班了
I gotta get to work.
我有个提议  想想就开心
You know what would make me happy?
什么提议
You know, what's that?
就是我们四个聚一聚
If the four of us could all, you know, hang out together.
艾蜜莉这周末要过来
In fact, Emily's coming into town this weekend.
要不要星期天晚上一起吃饭
What do you say we all have dinner, say Sunday night?
太好了
That would be great!
那就这么说定了
All right. All right. It's a date!
撑着点  你才撑着点
"Hang in there." You hang in there.
-你说什么  -没有  我只是在唱歌
- Did you say something? - No, just singing.
天啊
Oh, my God!
你看这件
Look at this one!
-好美哦  -是啊
- It's so beautiful. - Yeah.
有一半的婚纱最后要跟着新娘子离婚
You know about half of these will end up getting divorced.
有什么可以帮忙  二位
May I help you ladies?
我来取请你们保留的婚纱
Yes, I'm here to pick up a dress that you have on hold.
请问登记姓名是
Yes, what's the name, please?
-艾蜜莉·华森  -有  已经准备好了
- Emily Waltham. - Yes, I have it right here.
你要试穿吗  华森小姐
Would you like to try it on, Miss Waltham?
好啊
Okay.
你是我见过最美的新娘
You're the most beautiful bride I've ever seen.
可不是嘛
I am, aren't I?
-华森小姐  -怎么了
- Miss Waltham? - Yes?
我们要打佯了
We're closing.
好吧
All right.
请把戒指还给我
And could I get my ring back?
兄弟  该翻身了
All right, buddy. Time to roll over.
不要啊  瞎了我的狗眼
No, no! No, no, no, no!
你一定要去诊所  你要去诊所
You are going to a clinic! You're going to a clinic!
再去趟睡衣店
And a pajama store!
她用过杯子了吗
Does she use the cups?
对  她用过了
Yes, I believe she does.
她用过盘子了吗  对  她用过了
Does she use the plates? Yes, I believe she does!
谢谢
Thank you.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
-等一下  -不行  让我进去
- Just a second. - No, no! Let me in!
-是菲比吗  -是我
- Phoebe? - Yeah.
等一下好吗
Can you hold on a minute?
不行  现在就让我进去
No! You have to let me in right now!
-只有你自己吗  -对
- Are you alone? - Yes.
好吧
All right.
真讨厌
This sucks.
我不知道去睡眠诊所
I don't know I have to stay up all night
前一晚还不能睡觉
before I go to the stupid sleep clinic.
我好累
I'm so tired.
现在才六点
It's six o'clock.
听说你跟约书亚
I hear you and Joshua
要和罗斯跟艾蜜莉吃饭
are going out to dinner with Ross and Emily.
我觉得这么做很有风度
I think that's really cool.
是啊  瑞秋  你处理得很好
Yeah, Rach. I think you're handling that really well.
处理
"Handling it"?
什么处不处理  根本没什么好处理的
What do you mean, handling it? There's nothing to handle.
如果没跟约书亚在一起
Maybe I'd have a problem with this
我或许会无法接受
if it wasn't for me and Joshua.
反正他们也结不成婚
They're not going to get married anyway.
什么
What?
他们搞这种闪电式订婚  简直可笑
Come on. They rushed into this thing so fast, it's ridiculous!
他们订完婚要等一年左右再结婚吧
They'll be engaged for like what? A year?
在这段时间里
And somewhere along the way,
他们总会有人察觉到不对头
one of them is gonna realise what they've done
然后取消婚约
and they're gonna call the whole thing off.
你们等不到在他们婚礼上跳舞
I'm telling you, you'll be dancing at my wedding
就会先参加我的婚礼
before you dance at theirs.
我参加婚礼从不跳舞
You know, I don't dance at weddings.
为什么
Why not?
因为婚礼是结识异性的好地方
Because weddings are a great place to meet women.
而我跳舞是这副德性
When I dance, I look like this.
你好
Hey, man.
4周后的今天你们有事吗
What are you guys doing four weeks from today?
-没事  -没事
- Nothing. - Nothing.
我...
I am...
有空
free.
太好了  我和艾蜜莉一个月后要结婚
Great. Because Emily and I are getting married in a month.
-什么  -没错
- What? - Yep.
-一个月后  -对
- In a month? - Yeah.
-你是说30天后  -对
- You mean 30 days? - Yeah.
-从今天算起  -对
- From now? - Yeah.
太棒了
That's great!
她一直想跟她父母
Emily always wanted to get married in this beautiful place
在同一个地方结婚
that her parents got married,
但那里马上就要拆了  所以...
but it's getting torn down, so...
我知道这很疯狂
I know it's crazy,
但我们之间从头到尾都很疯狂
but everything up till now has been so crazy
就是感觉很对味
and it just feels right.
那是我经期的第二天
Hey, that's the day after I start menstruating!
这不是我的
This isn't mine.
-瑞秋  -嗨
- Hey, Rachel. - Hi.
你好吗
What's up?
你电话里的声音听着好尖
Your voice sounded all squeaky on the phone.
没事  我只是想见你
Nothing. I just wanted to see you.
见见你  抱抱你
See you and hug you.
见见你
See you...
真好
Great!
坐
Sit.
你还好吗
You okay?
好得不得了  我非常非常开心
I'm more than okay. I am really, really happy.
你想知道为什么吗
Want to know why?
我想吗
Do I?
因为我对我们的关系很满意
Because I am really happy about us.
我觉得我们进展得特别顺利
I think we are so on the right track.
我们很般配  我们很来电
I think we are working. I think we are clicking.
-你懂吗  -当然懂
- You know? - Yeah, sure, sure.
我们很来电
We're clicking.
如果说有什么小缺撼
If there was just one little area where
我们需要加强的
I think we need to work on, I would think
应该就是我们不够疯狂
it's that we're just not crazy enough.
老实说  我不太同意
I got to say, I'm not too sure I agree with that.
你说得对
You know, yeah, you're right.
我们相处得很开心  但是...
We have our fun. Yeah? But...
我是说要再疯狂一点  你懂吗
I mean, like crazy! You know?
好吧
Okay. All right.
这件事听起来会有点仓促
This is going to sound, you know, a little hasty.
但你听我说就行
But just go with me.
我们结婚吧
What if we got married?
-什么  -我知道  你会觉得...
- What? - Oh, I know. It's so totally like...
"哇  我们可以这么做吗 "
"Whoa, can we do this?" You know?
但感觉就是很对  你不觉得吗
But it just feels right. Don't you think it does?
感觉真的很对  你不...
I mean, it just feels right. Don't you...?
瑞秋
Rachel...
你是个...
you're...
非常...
a real...
特别的姑娘
special lady.
但我的离婚还没办完
But my divorce isn't final yet
而且我们只约会过4次
and we've been on four dates.
所以我是想说...不要...
So I'm thinking: No...
不过...
but...
谢了
thanks.
你这个白痴
You idiot!
-姓名  -乔伊·崔比安尼
- Your name, please? - Joey Tribbiani.
你是否整夜没睡  准备接受诊疗
Did you stay up all night in preparation for your sleep study?
先生
Sir?
对  他没睡
Yes, he did.
好的  待会就叫您
All right. We'll call you in a few minutes.
你看那个女生好辣
Check out that girl. She's really hot.
是啊
Yeah, she is.
你好吗
How're you doing?
-怎样  -你在跟整间候诊室的人搭汕
- What? - You're coming on to the entire room.
-我是钱德勒  -我是玛乔莉
- I'm Chandler. - I'm Marjorie.
-我可以坐吗  -请便
- Do you mind if I sit? - Please.
你来做什么治疗
So what are you in for?
我会说梦话
I talk in my sleep.
真巧  我专听梦话
What a coincidence! I listen in my sleep.
给我留个电话嘛
So why don't you give me your number?
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Are you ready? - Yeah.
我接到了  我的
I got it! Mine!
-恭喜你  -谢谢
- Congratulations! - Thank you!
换我换我
My turn, my turn!
准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
你扔得太不准了
That was a terrible throw!
我才不要直接扔给你  太假了
I won't throw it right to you. That's not real.
你看我  穿成这样我还在乎假不假吗
Look at me. My big concern is what's real?
天啊
Oh, my God!
我们真的很可悲  对吧
We're really sad, aren't we?
没错
Yeah, I think we are.
这都不是我的婚纱
This isn't even my dress.
你起码不是去
At least you didn't rent yours
"还不晚婚纱店"租的
from a store called "It's Not Too Late."
-我要换掉了  -我也是
- I'm changing out of this. - Me, too.
半小时后再换
In like half an hour?
我也是
Me, too.
这次直接扔给我
All right, now throw it straight this time.
我要结婚了
I'm getting married!
我现在好讨厌普通衣服
I hate my regular clothes now.
低头一看就知道
I look down and I know
今天不是我人生最特别的日子
this won't be the most special day of my life.
一开始还感觉挺好玩的
I mean, it was kind of fun for a while...
不过  你不觉得有点蠢吗
but didn't you start to feel kind of silly?
是有点
I guess.
天啊
Oh, my God!
你太不厚道了
You're such a cheater!
小可爱们
Hello, little ones.
-乔伊打鼾的毛病能治好吗   -能
- So, is Joey going to stop snoring? - Yep!
而且有个美女答应跟我约会
And a beautiful woman agreed to go out with me.
乔伊本来想约她  但她选了我
Joey wanted to ask her out, but, you know, she picked me.
怎么会
How'd that happen?
因为我比较酷
Because I'm cooler.
不  说真的
No, seriously.
她是那种...乔伊睡死了
She's the kind of girl... Joey was unconscious.
你们好吗
Hey, you guys! What's happening?
天啊
Oh, my God!
那是什么
What is that?
这是睡眠诊所给我的
They gave it to me at the sleep clinic...
可以防止我打鼾
and it's going to help me not to snore.
那你现在在睡觉吗  乔伊
Well, are you asleep right now, Joe?
睡觉时候才用戴
Because I don't think you have to wear it unless you are.
我当然知道
I know I don't have to.
这玩意味道不错
It tastes good.
而且看起来很酷
Plus, you look cool.
我刚给约书亚打了电话
I just called Joshua.
情况怎样
How'd it go?
我尽力劝他说
I did my best to convince him
我不是什么恨嫁的疯婆子
that I'm not some crazy girl who's dying to get married.
我只是情绪低落而已
And I'm going through a hard time.
他怎么说
What'd he say?
他的答录机非常体谅我
His answering machine was very understanding.
我好郁闷
I feel blue.
亲爱的
Sweetie.
他一定会再找你的
I bet you anything that he'll call you again.
或许吧  但我觉得自己根本不在乎
Yeah, maybe. But, you know, I don't think I even care.
我觉得让我郁闷的不是他
I don't think he's the one I'm sad about.
虽然我说过不在意罗斯结婚的事情
I know I said I'm totally okay with Ross getting married.
但是实际上...
But as it turns out...
我觉得自己的心态没调整好
I don't think I'm handling it all that well.
或许吧
Yeah, maybe.
我正在想这是为什么
And I'm just trying to figure out why.
想到了吗
Any luck?
罗斯和我不是一直分分合合嘛
You know how Ross and I have always been on-again, off-again?
我一直觉得将来的某个时候
I guess I just figured, somewhere down the road...
我们会再复合...
we would be on again.
再分手
Again.
我们都这么觉得
You know what? I think we all did.
我订了星期天晚上的餐厅
I got us reservations for Sunday night.
9点在厄尼之家行吗
How about Ernie's at 9:00?
你还是改成3个吧
Well, you'd better make it for three.
下午3点我们应该还不饿
I don't know if we're going to be hungry at three.
是3个人
Three people.
约书亚不去了
Joshua's not going to be there.
怎么了
What happened?
他应该是跟我分手了
Well, I think he broke up with me.
天啊  为什么
No. Why?
他太容易受惊了
Apparently, he scares easy.
瑞秋  我很遗撼
Rachel, I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
人生不如意  十有八九
Sometimes things don't work out the way you thought they would.
过来
Come here.
-你不用去接艾蜜莉吗  -是哦
- Don't you have to go pick up Emily? - Yeah.
-你不要紧吗  -没事  我有姐妹们陪着
- Are you okay? - Yeah. I got my girls.
有件事可能会让你开心起来
Hey, you know what might cheer you up?
什么
What?
说实话
I got to tell you...
我的心情真的好多了
this really does put me in a better mood.
真希望有整天穿婚纱的工作
I wish there was a job where I could wear this all the time.
也许以后会有
Maybe someday there will be.
完了  是钱德勒
Oh, god. That's Chandler,
他来借晚上约会的蜡烛
he's coming by to borrow candles for his big date.
瑞秋  别开门  他会看见的
Rachel, don't get it! He'll see us!
新郎不能看见新娘
The groom cannot see the bride.
我又不嫁钱德勒
I'm not going to marry Chandler.
见了当然就嫁不成了
Not after this!
你们放轻松就好
Okay guys, just relax.
我愿意
I do!
我得走了
I got to go.
约书亚  约书亚
Jo-Joshua! Joshua!
好吧  吓跑他很正常
Yeah, well, that ought to do it.
吃的在这里  很好
Food's here. Fair enough.
15分钟预警
Fifteen-minute warning.
迟了
Late.
老兄  我还要睡觉呢
Dude, I am trying to sleep!